let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1.At what rate percent per annum will a sum of money double in 8 years?",
    answer: "12.5%",
    options: [
      "12.5%",
      "13.5%",
      "11.5%",
      "14.5%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "2.The sum required to earn a monthly interest of Rs 400 at 10 % per annum at simple interest is?",
    answer: " Rs 2000",
    options: [
      " Rs 2000",
      " Rs 12000",
      " Rs 24000",
      " Rs 48000",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 3. If A's height is 40% less than that of B, how much percent B's height is more than that of A?",
    answer: " 66.66%",
    options: [
      " 66.66%",
      " 76.66%",
      " 96.66%",
      " 86.66%"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "4. Which e-learning platform has been featured in Time Magazine's 2021 list of 100 most influential companies?",
    answer: "BYJU's",
    options: [
      "BYJU's",
      "Edukart",
      "Unacademy",
      "Toppr",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "5. The cost price of 20 articles is the same as the selling price of x articles. If the profit is 25%, then the value of x is?",
      answer: "16",
      options: [
        "15",
        "16",
        "18",
        "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "6.  A clock is started at noon. By 10 minutes past 5, the hour hand has turned through?",
    answer: "155°",
    options: [
      "145°",
      "150°",
      "155°",
      "160°",
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "7. What was the day of the week on 28th May, 2006?",
  answer: "Sunday",
  options: [
    "Thursday",
    "Friday",
    "Saturday",
    "Sunday",
]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "8. The average of 20 numbers is zero. Of them, at the most, how many may be greater than zero?",
  answer: "19",
  options: [
    "0",
    "1",
    "10",
    "19"
]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "9. The banker's gain of a certain sum due 2 years hence at 10% per annum is Rs. 24. The present worth is?",
  answer: "Rs. 600",
  options: [
    "Rs. 480",
    "Rs. 520",
    "Rs. 600",
    "Rs. 960"
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "10.What least number must be added to 1056, so that the sum is completely divisible by 23 ?",
  answer: "2",
  options: [ 
    "2",
    "3",
    "18",
    "21"
]
},

];